http://www.dcsltd.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyWe ask that you read this privacy notice carefully as it contains important information on who we are, how and why we collect, store, use and share personal information, your rights in relation to your personal information and on how to contact us and supervisory authorities in the event you have a complaint.Who we areData Conversion Systems Ltd collects, uses and is responsible for certain personal information about you. When we do so we are regulated under the General Data Protection Regulation which applies across the European Union (including in the United Kingdom) and we are responsible as ‘controller’ of that personal information for the purposes of those laws.The personal information we collect and useInformation collected by usIn the course of Product Registration, Technical Support, Contact Forms and Marketing News we collect the following personal information when you provide it to us:Full NameAddressEmail addressPhone numbersHow we use your personal informationWe use your personal information:To provide you with marketing information if you indicate that you want to receive such informationTo improve our products and services and provide technical support for our productsTo help us analyse website usage in order to develop our site in accordance with your needsWho we share your personal information withWe will not share your personal information with any third party without your consent. This may include a Certified dCS Dealer or Distributor that is local to you and could therefore be the right contact to demo our products, attend events of interest or assist with technical support. If we feel this would be in your interest we would only share your details after proactively obtaining your consent.Whether information has to be provided by you, and if so whyThe provision of name, address, phone number and email address is required from you to enable us to register your product or handle technical support or warranty enquiries. We will inform you at the point of collecting information from you, whether you are required to provide the information to us.How long your personal information will be keptWe will hold name, address and contact details for the period we are required to retain this information by applicable UK tax law, which is currently 6 years.Reasons we can collect and use your personal informationWe have a number of lawful reasons that we can use (or ‘process’) your personal information. One of the lawful reasons is called ‘legitimate interests’.Broadly speaking Legitimate Interests means that we can process your personal information if:We have a genuine and legitimate reason and we are not harming any of your rights and interestsThis means when you provide your personal details to us we use your information for our legitimate business interests to continue to improve our service and products. Before doing this we will carefully consider and balance any potential impact on you and your rights.Some typical examples of when we might use the approach are for preventing fraud, direct marketing, maintaining the security of our system, data analytics, enhancing, modifying or improving our services, identifying usage trends and determining the effectiveness of our campaigns.Your rightsUnder the General Data Protection Regulation you have a number of important rights free of charge. In summary, those include rights to:Fair processing of information and transparency over how we use your use personal informationAccess to your personal information and to certain other supplementary information that this Privacy Notice is already designed to addressRequire us to correct any mistakes in your information which we holdRequire the erasure of personal information concerning you in certain situationsReceive the personal information concerning you which you have provided to us, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and have the right to transmit those data to a third party in certain situationsObject at any time to processing of personal information concerning you for direct marketingObject to decisions being taken by automated means which produce legal effects concerning you or similarly significantly affect youObject in certain other situations to our continued processing of your personal informationOtherwise restrict our processing of your personal information in certain circumstances For further information on each of those rights, including the circumstances in which they apply, see the Guidance from the UK Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) on individuals rights under the General Data Protection Regulation.If you would like to exercise any of those rights, please:Email, call or write to usLet us have enough information to identify youlet us have proof of your identity and address (a copy of your driving licence or passport and a recent Utility or credit card bill), andLet us know the information to which your request relatesIf you would like to unsubscribe from any email newsletter you can also click on the ‘unsubscribe’ button at the bottom of the newsletters. It may take up to 5 days for this to take place.Keeping your personal information secureWe have appropriate security measures in place to prevent personal information from being accidentally lost, or used or accessed in an unauthorised way. We limit access to your personal information to those who have a genuine business need to know it. Those processing your information will do so only in an authorised manner and are subject to a duty of confidentiality.We also have procedures in place to deal with any suspected data security breach. We will notify you and any applicable regulator of a suspected data security breach where we are legally required to do so.If you want detailed information from Get Safe Online on how to protect your information and your computers and devices against fraud, identity theft, viruses and many other online problems, please visit www.getsafeonline.org. Get Safe Online is supported by HM Government and leading businesses.How to complainWe hope that we can resolve any query or concern you raise about our use of your information.The General Data Protection Regulation also gives you right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the European Union (or European Economic Area) state where you work, normally live or where any alleged infringement of data protection laws occurred. The supervisory authority in the UK is the Information Commissioner who may be contacted at https://ico.org.uk/concerns/ or telephone: 0303 123 1113.Changes to this privacy noticeThis privacy notice was published on 11-5-2018 and last updated on 11-5-2018.We may change this privacy notice from time to time, when we do we will inform you via email.How to contact usPlease contact us if you have any questions about this privacy notice or the information we hold about you.If you wish to contact us, please send an email to info@dcsltd.co.uk, write to Data Conversion Systems Ltd Unit 1, Buckingway Business Park, Swavesey, Cambridgeshire, CB24 4AE or call 01954 233950.FacebookTwitterInstagram © 2020 Data Conversion Systems LtdDistributorsPressSitemapTerms & PoliciesContact Us
